[Nurse's Office]
This is humiliating
You awake?
Uh, yeah
I'm sorry
I spread the rumor
that you
like Hyeon-wu
to mess with you
I already explained
it to everyone
It felt like
I overstepped a line
I'm good
at keeping boundaries
Right?
You…
call that an apology?
I apologize
and you still complain
I carried you here
What?
Hey! Move!
Hey! Get out of the way
d*** it!
Stop blocking the way!
Get lost!
Move! Move!
What the hell?
Fine, I get it
I won't overstep
when I tease you
Happy now?
We're friends
Right?
Sure
We should get back
to class
[Daemun School Trip]
The highlight of
school is
the school trip
On this important day
I'm…
F***
And this a**hole…
hasn't changed at all